# **Tad Heigel**

2541 North Pleasantburg Drive, Suite 253 Greenville SC, 29609 theig072@gmail.com (231) 670-7640

#### **About Me**

For the last six years I have worked in telecommunications developing innovative programs that focused on organizational strategy and human capital growth. I oversaw two states and was responsible for developing our stores, teams and talent. In January 2014, I made the distinct decision to switch careers and pursue hacking fulltime. Why? I believe the ability to create what I imagine is true freedom. I want to be a part of something greater than money and build real solutions that benefit others.

I am relatively new to the tech world, but have been dabbling with Wordpress and my own startup ideas for the last two years. My goal as a freshly hatched frontend developer is to solve problems that matter by getting involved with companies and projects that are making a difference.

#### **Technical Skills**

iTerminal - Sublime - FileZilla - NPM - Yeoman - Homebrew - Grunt - Bower - Git - HTML5 - CSS3 - SASS - Bootstrap - Modernizer - Bourbon - Javascript - jQuery - UnderscoreJS - JSON - Ajax - BackboneJS - Parse - Mocha - Chai - Heroku - Wordpress - Word - Excel - Powerpoint - Staff Development - Curriculum Creation - Sales Training - Customer Service

## **Personal Characteristics**

- Motivated
- Leads by example
- Problem Solver
- Excellent interpersonal and communication skills
- Dedicated to accomplishing tasks correctly

- Meticulous with an exceptional attention for detail
- Poised and competent
- Can make and execute knowledgeable decisions quickly
- Able to work under pressure while upholding standards
- Will work until the job is complete

# **Experience**

The Iron Yard

Frontend Student

**Carmichael Wireless** 

Director of Development Wireless Workshop Leader District Leader Store Manager

T-Mobile

Wireless Consultant

**Carmichael Wireless** 

Assistant Manager Sales/Customer Service Representative Greenville, SC

April 2014 - July 2014

Greenville, SC

December 2012 - January 2014 August 2012 - January 2014 December 2011 - December 2012 June 2009 - December 2011

Simpsonville, SC

December 2008 - April 2009

Greenville, SC

May 2008 - December 2008 January 2008 - May 2008

## **Career Accomplishments**

- Track record of rapid promotion based on performance, work ethic, and ability to multitask
- Multiple "Salesman of the Month" plaques 2008-2010
- ❖ Salesman of the year (2008) Carmichael Wireless
- Youngest employee ever within Carmichael Wireless to be promoted to Management (2008)
- Only store manager placed on wireless committee board meetings

### **Education**

- FCS of Fremont Graduated Valedictorian
- Attended Bob Jones Fine Arts University
  - Major Social Studies Education
  - Minor Music Education

- Able to continuously develop and train award winning sales teams
- Raised monthly profits by over 500% as store manager
  - > 2010 Carmichael Wireless TPS of the year
  - > 2011 Carmichael Wireless TPS of the year
  - 2011 BEST Ind. VZW Net Promoter Score of the year SO-CAR
  - 2012 Carmichael Wireless TPS of the year

# Links

- Github: https://github.com/Thaddeous
- Portfolio: http://thaddeous.github.io/Personal-Portfolio/